I'm out of here.
>> Don't get all queasy on me now, Trixie.
You were the one who offered to help.
>> I only volunteered to stop you from
roping my sister into into whatever this
is. I thought you needed help moving
stuff.
>> Oh my god, we are moving stuff. It just
happens to be boxes with corpses inside
them.
>> You're insane.
>> No, I'm a mortician.
>> You're cutting apart dead ponies.
>> Well, someone has to. You think ponies
just magically scoop out their own
inards when they die? That's my job,
sugar mama. I remove, clean, and
sometimes I get to accessorize beautiful
mares that pass on through. Accessorize.
There's an art in this line of work
tricks. Making sure mares look perfect
for their final curtain call. That's my
thing. If your sister ever, you know,
passes away, I want to be the one to
prep her body. I'll give her the send
off she deserves.
>> There's intestines in your pocket.
Oh, how did that get in there?
>> You're [__] up. Why does everybody say
that to me?
>> Marionette, I told you to stop visiting
during work hours. It makes me look
soft.
>> I made egg salad sandwiches. You're not
overworking yourself again, are you?
Your shift ended 4 hours ago.
>> You need to stop bringing food to work,
[__] You know it all goes straight to
my butt.
You're the only pony who talks to me
anymore. You know that, Mary?
>> Oh, I'm sure that's not true.
>> It is. No one else can tolerate me.
You're the only one that keeps coming
back. Like I'm something worth sticking
around for. You're exaggerating.
>> Am I? Because lately it feels like even
you've been drifting away. You've got
this shiny new family in Trixie,
Twilight, and Flawless. And you light up
so much when you talk about them. You
used to light up like that when you talk
about me. Sometimes I think I'll die in
a ditch somewhere and you won't even
notice. You'll just go on like I never
existed. Don't say that. You're a very
dear friend to me. I thought we were
more than that. But I guess I was wrong
again.
You're twisting things to make me feel
guilty. Twilight told me you would do
this.
>> I'm just thinking about how much I've
hurt you. To think that what we had
actually meant something once. But it's
fine. You've got other ponies now.
You were the one who broke up with me. I
totally forgot about that part. You'll
at least stay while I eat, won't you?
>> I got to get back home and watch Iron
Chef.
You can't park there. That spot is for
handicapped citizens. Um, well,
actually, [__] if you could read, you
would know that sign over there says
this parking spot is for people with big
asses, which I very clearly have. So,
why don't you just silence that pie hole
and mind your own business, [__]
That's not what it means.
>> Uh, yeah, it does. Why do you think that
dude has a big [__] butt? Unless you
want to come over here and fight about
it.
Damn, I think I pooped a little bit.
I'll just head inside for some chicken
and waffles. Then I can get back home
and watch Iron Chef on the Food Network.
Or maybe some of that gay porn bulk
biceps told me about. Jesus Christ, your
ass is thick as [__] with like three
C's. Dead ass. What's your name, [__]
Oh, it's not that big. Oh, yeah, it is.
It's like two really big oranges. What's
your name, dude? We should go somewhere
and have sex. I'm Thorax. Thorax? More
like your ass. What time do you get off,
you naughty little cupcake? Um, I I get
off at 5.
I'll swing by with my big ass pickup
truck to see if we can do something
later. Oh, all right then. Sounds fun.
What are we going to do?
Maybe we'll head down to the lake and
feed duck some bread or some [__] Just
you and me. But wouldn't that be gay?
Only a little bit. I think I'll leave
you with your imagination as I walk away
while you gaze upon my fat butt crack.
Hey, baby girl. I see you have a purse
like Tinky Winky from the Teletubbies.
That's pretty sexy. You know, Tinky
Winky has the biggest ass out of all the
Teletubbies.
Oh. Uh, I don't watch the Teletubbies.
Oh, well, neither do I. Teletubbies is
for babies. Get in the back with the hay
and cow [__] I need the passenger seat
to carry all of the [__] bananas I
just bought.
You watch the Teletubbies? I think
that's actually really sweet. Most of
the guys I know are afraid to show their
soft sides because it make people think
they're gay or some [__] That's why
people make fun of me because I'm green
and soft compared to most changelings.
Cool. People make fun of me because I
have big muscles. I I think your muscles
are pretty nice, actually. Did I ask for
your opinion, [__]
Tear Rick, are you okay? You haven't
said a thing for 32 hours. I I can't
bring myself to do this thorax. It's
fine. There's no one around to see us
suck balls. We can be as gay as we want.
Not that. You need to run, Thorax. Run
away. Run far away and never come back
before he gets here. Who? Before who
gets here? T- Rick, you're scaring me.
>> Ah, so you are this Thorax T- Rick told
me so much about. You really do have a
big booty. You did well, Tyreek. And to
top it all off, it's just as you said.
He really does look like the Nickelodeon
logo. You definitely bagged me a fine
one tonight.
>> T Rick talks about me.
>> I am prepared to purchase him now for 15
cents.
>> Huh? You sold me for 15? 20. But he
talked me down a nickel.
>> No butts, T Rick. Unless you want yours
pounded by me. We had a deal that you
would bring the man to me. You will
honor the deal or face serious
consequences.
>> Triick, what is he saying? You didn't
invite me here to feed ducks at all, did
you? You were planning on selling me
like a fine cut of Wagyu beef. Thorax,
that's not true. I mean, it was at the
start, but then I got to know you and
please let me explain. To think I was
going to suck your huge sweaty balls. I
mean, you still can. Nobody is stopping
you.
Please, Daddy. I can make up for my
betrayal. I'll suck your sweaty balls.
>> The time for that is gone, fool. I gave
you and your [__] stained ass one job
and you committed to it. For that you
have earned my friendship and respect.
Do not attempt to do anything that would
make me take that away, Tyrek. Like I
took away your right to wear pants.
>> Stop crying. You're a man and men are
not allowed to cry unless they are
within the face of God himself.
>> Leave him alone.
Haha. You dare to stand up to me, little
man? Let's see if your bite is as
sorrowful as your bark.
>> Prince Blueb Blood, you are under arrest
for kidnapping and pony trafficking. Get
away from him.
>> What?
>> I said get away from him.
>> Sorry, I had headphones on.
>> No,
you won't get away with this shining
armor. I already paid 10 cents in
advance for a claim on his ass if you
take him now. I will call the cops and
file a claim of petty theft.
>> Thorax, wait, don't leave my dump truck
of an ass.
>> Come on. We might not be able to save
his dump truck, but we can use his
pickup truck to escape. The Canterlot
royal guards will take care of the rest
here.
>> No, I won't leave Triick behind. He
tried to save me.
>> [__] he tried to sell you. Oh, yeah, I
forgot. Bye, Triick. [__] you. Shining
armor is my new daddy.
>> I'll take the wheel, gave boy. You sit
in the passenger seat. Watch the
bananas.
>> It's fine. I'm gay.
[__]
>> How did you know where I was?
>> Prince Blueb Bloodler [__] that he
thinks are hot ass into that forest so
he can buy them in secret. I was going
there to try and arrest him, but I
didn't plan on you being there.
Apparently, you were going to be his
next toy.
>> Well, is he going to let me go home? I
have to catch the new episode of Iron
Chef.
>> Don't count on it, kid. You are number
one on his list now. And the fact that
you got away only excites him more. He's
not going to let up until he gets that
lime green ass. Oh my [__] god. This
is almost the worst day of my life. Hey,
want to make out?
>> I'm not gay.
>> This is the worst day of my life.
Why are we stopping? I have to get out
of town. Are you going to press me up
against the outside of the car and rape
me? No, I just got to pee.
>> Then you're going to come back and rape
me?
Holy crackers. That guy just whipped out
his goods to pee on the side of the road
like it's no pony's business. What an
alpha. I got to take a little tinkle out
of my balls, too.
You picked a bad time and place to empty
your [__] balls cuz I'm having a
really [__] night.
YO.
YO. Holy [__] He's dead.
>> Thorax. Oh god. No. You are among the
only 154 men I ever loved.
>> Flawless. Are you free? I need someone
to distract me so I don't self harm
tonight.
Okay, I've thought about it and I've
decided you're going to help me win
Marionette back. Uh,
>> and how exactly am I supposed to do
that? Ask her to forgive your years of
being a controlling [__]
>> No, you're going to be mean to her. I
don't follow insult that Lesb's
appearance and make her feel like [__]
That's the sort of stuff I do that
triggers abandonment issues in her.
Starlight, this is bananas.
>> It's psychology flawless. Sociopathism
is all lesbians have ever known. She
won't even be mad at you because she
expects everyone who shows her
compassion to eventually stab her in the
back anyway. It's like muscle memory,
similar to how a cat is drawn to milk. I
have a better idea. Nothing is better
than psychological warfare. You go over
there and tell Marionette how much she
means to you like a normal pony. See,
this is how I can tell you're straight
because lesbians don't do that. We rage
bait each other until the other one is
graveling in the dirt. Do you want her
back or not? I'm weighing my options.
You know what? [__] it. We ball.
So, this is where you've been. Pooky.
Look, I know this is sudden and the
number of times we broke up is in the
four digits, but I want to get back
together. Oh, you're right. This is
sudden. Uh, I don't really want to.
>> Girl, you best start making sense before
I drag you outside and curb stomp you in
front of all the kids.
>> I'm not in the mood to date anyone right
now. In fact, I quite like being on my
own. I don't have to split my tokens.
>> Something is wrong. She said no to me
because you didn't even try. You just
said words. I don't have time for this.
I'm going to get a cheese pizza.
God, how many fits are there in this
[__] town?
>> Hey, if we bought a Nintendo Switch,
too, we could all play together.
>> Oh my god, being annoying.
>> Hey, how much for that Nintendo Switch,
too?
>> 1,000 tickets. But if I were you, I
wouldn't even bother. There's been
ponies here who's been playing games for
days to win that [__]
Well, fortunately, none of those ponies
are as flawless as I am. Just you watch
Lyra and Bon Bon. I'll win those tickets
before you know it.
>> Okay.
>> Hey, Bozo, you trying to get us thrown
out of here? I don't think you should be
messing with the wires like that. Rules
and boundaries don't apply to me. Well,
they apply to me. And though you got the
bakery back there, I ain't got the bread
for a cash bond. Bam. Easy.
Take these tickets, trade them in, and
buy that switch too for Marionette, and
she'll love you forever.
>> Hey, the wires on this machine are all
cut up. She hacked it.
>> She's ruining the wholesome family image
of Chuck-E-Cheese.
>> I ain't done, diddly squat. Stop
annoying me.
>> Come on, Dashy. You're supposed to be
the best at everything. Be the best at
tickets and get me my Switch.
>> I'm trying my best, [__] You think I
like losing to a bunch of pizza grease
covered babies?
>> Then do better before I call my sister
Limestone here to spank you like she
does to me when I've been a naughty
girl.
>> Hey hacker girl. Heard you rewired the
jackpot machine earlier. Think you can
hook up a bad [__]
>> Sorry, my hacker days are over. Can't
blame the girl. If my hair only had five
colors in it, I would.
No one is winning that switch but
Starlight.
>> Pinkie Pie, take our tickets and run. We
can't let them find out we have 999
tickets already.
>> Okie dokie.
>> Over my dead, artificially perfect body.
Starlight. She's escaping through the
ventilation shaft. You may be able to
squeeze on through, but my huge kioat
literally could never. Let's go through
the back way and see if we can cut her
off.
>> You'll never find me in here.
>> You go up there. I'll see if she went
this way. Flawless. Wait. You're my best
friend.
Stop chasing me, freak.
I'm not chasing you. I'm flawless. I'm
reclaiming what's mine. I'm flawless.
No, you're the reflection. I'm the
original. What's your earliest memory?
Did it go like this?
That's gross. Put your head back on.
A little over a year ago, Twilight cast
a spell on us which split me away from
you. I managed to survive by escaping to
mirror world. But those actions meant
you my extraordinarily more autistic
side would take over until I got strong
enough to contact you.
>> Yippee.
>> You expect me to believe that?
>> You're obsessed with the idea of
perfection, but only in creating it.
Like the perfect friends or perfect
family? What are you getting at? My
point is that flawless doesn't create
perfection. She is it. Well, if that's
what makes you think you're the
original, then good for you. I built
this family so all of us could be happy.
I gave Twilight something she secretly
longed for, a family and marionette a
home. In other words, you're my shadow.
The one who wants to fix everything I
broke. A pony born from guilt. And you
think that makes you better?
>> No, it just makes me lucky because I get
to experience something you never do.
And what's that?
>> Love. You think I don't know what love
is?
>> Well, how can you? You're so bad.
>> You don't understand me.
>> Maybe not. But I think I understand
enough to feel sorry for you.
>> It's over, Pinkie Pie. Now hand over my
tickets.
>> You can't have them. Get away from me.
You're just jealous cuz I'm about to get
the Switch, too. And you're not.
What in Equestria? Why is there a secret
basement dungeon under Chuck E-Cheese?
>> Fool. It is because of you that Thorax
escaped my grasp. I was going to
purchase him as a servant. And now,
thanks to you, he roams free. For your
transgressions, you shall rot in my
personal dungeon.
>> Dude, I'm so [__] sorry this
happened. Can you just like let me go?
Shut up, little man. To start your
punishment, you shall play 5 minutes of
THIS GAME. YO,
>> HOLY [__]
>> Come on, man. That game sucks worse than
Overwatch, too.
>> And if you manage to hold out, I shall
bring you a slice of pizza and bread
sticks from upstairs. And then you may
suck on hairy nuts.
>> We have to get down there and save him.
No pony should be subjected to playing a
hero shooter game in this current year.
>> Pass. It's a statistical fact that men
cause like 95% of global problems.
>> Yeah, I'm just here for tickets.
>> You can't just ignore a gay evil prince
enslaving homosexual men under a Chuck
E. Cheese.
>> Why not? It's been going on so far and
we didn't even notice.
>> You two make for terrible superheroes.
We're all middle-aged women gambling in
a children's restaurant to steal a
Nintendo console from babies. We aren't
exactly the pinnacle of excellence.
Tell me, T- Rick, have you ever heard of
the game Russian roulette?
>> No, I'm American.
>> Well, you'll catch on soon enough, I'm
sure. But you see, I play it a little
differently. Instead of one bullet, I
use five.
>> You can't do this to me. Blueb blood.
>> You see, I find bullet rather boring.
They don't provide the same thrill as
other options. So, if a one in five
chance occurs and you survive not being
shot in the head, I shall rip a massive
beef stew in your face instead. That
way. You wish you would be dead.
>> Oh god, just shoot me in the ass.
>> Oh, god damn it.
>> There's no time for death here, Triick.
Just me and my farting ass. And I fear
the game's only just begun.
>> A thousand tickets, baby. The Switch 2
is mine.
>> Congratulations, Starlight. You've done
it. You've officially proven that you're
one big [__]
>> Excuse me. What's with the attitude?
You're acting like a lesbian. I thought
you wanted me to win the switch.
>> I said that to motivate you, not to fuel
your descent into moral manipulation.
You were supposed to win her heart, but
instead you're fighting for control
again. You think if you buy Marionette a
switch, she'll just come running into
your arms?
>> Yes.
>> I'm not trying to make you feel bad,
Starlike. I just want you to see what
you're doing. You think this is how you
prove love?
>> No, I I don't think that way.
I don't think that way because I don't
even know the first thing about love. I
just want her to look at me like she
used to. But she can't even do that
anymore because she hides behind a
stupid mask.
>> Here, take them before I change my mind.
>> You're giving them back to me. But why?
Because I don't want them anymore. You
were the one who earned them.
Pooky, don't talk to me right now. I'm
counting tickets. Forget the switch.
Forget the switch? Have you lost your
mind? I'm only 952 tickets away from
winning it. I don't care about the
stupid console. Okay, I care about you.
I'd rather eat greasy pizza and talk
about Iron Chef with you than spend
another second doing something else. You
want to eat pizza with me? And for once,
you don't have to pay. Look, I wasn't
the best mayor friend for you. But the
truth is, I seriously do miss you.
And if you win that dumb console, we'll
see even less of each other. So, I
figured we could do something else, like
make friendship bracelets. I know it's a
bit childish and we're pushing 30. I'd
love to.
>> Friends and family, we'll see where that
gets you flawless.
>> Get up, you big idiot. I've got a job
for you.
>> You look like the bad guy him from the
Powerpuff Girls if he was a mayor with a
big ass. Who the [__] are you?
>> I don't know who that is, but it doesn't
matter who I am. You see this? This girl
killed your gay lover in the woods
earlier today.
>> She killed Bulk Biceps.
>> The other one
>> she killed Sheriff Silverstar.
>> she killed cheese sandwich.
>> The other one
>> she killed Sunburst.
>> It was a green one.
>> Oh my god. She killed Winsley.
You're going to have to spell it out for
me. I have a buttload of sex.
>> Thorax. She killed Thorax.
>> I don't know who that is.
Okay. Well, her girlfriend is here in
the building. I think she's due for a
little eye for an eye. Don't you agree?
>> I'm done listening to people. I'm going
to live my life the way I want to, not
as a killer like Thorax would have
wanted me to do.
>> Unfortunately, I don't think you have
much of a choice in the matter.
What the hell is that?
>> That's T- Rick. Oh well, it used to be.
Now he's just a monster on a rampage
with one thing on his mind. Revenge.
>> Holy [__]
>> See, one little pony amongst you
seemingly killed his lover tonight. And
that kind of pissed him off. He thinks
it's only fair that because you killed
his mate, he should kill yours.
I'll handle this. I've been itching to
kill something tonight.
>> All by yourself? Are you sure about
that? You don't even have magic.
>> You're right. I don't. But I have
something stronger than any magic.
Feminism.
>> What the [__] is that?
>> The secret side of me. I never let you
see. I keep a cage, but I can't control
it. So stay away from me.
I feel the rage and I just can't hold
it. It's on the wall in the closing in
the hole. It comes away and I can't
control it. Hiding under the bed.
Why won't somebody come and save me from
this?
It's just
a [__] feel like A MONSTER. I HATE
WHAT I BECOME.
I feel like a monster. I feel like a
monster.
locking key,
but I can't control that. My mouth,
bring me down. Why won't somebody come
and save me from this? Make it
I feel like a monster.
I feel like a monster. I feel like a
monster.
I feel like a monster.
>> You?
>> Yes. Me? The one who gave you power
beyond anything. your mortal body could
comprehend. And what do you do with it?
You lose to one little girl.
>> I can win. If you just give me a little
bit more power, I can vanquish my foes.
>> More? I gave you more than I thought you
would need, and you still failed. I'm
done with you.
Yo.
>> Yo. Holy [__]
Holy [__]
>> Holy [__]
King,
you're
She got in the gle.
as a good
body
Y
again.
Huh?
>> A [__] Nuggets. What is this place?
Where am I?
>> He's awake. I didn't expect him to wake
up so soon.
>> I'll go get Spike. He'll probably want
to talk to him. You wait right here.
Bulk Biceps.
>> Sparky, you stupid [__] You're not
supposed to use our real names.
>> Oops. Sorry. Bulk biceps. Be right back.
Damn it. I can't see in this.
Spike T Rick is awake.
>> Sparky. I'm in the process of taking a
shower and washing my dirty little
dragon ass. Couldn't this have waited
like 3 minutes.
>> I I just thought you'd want to know.
>> You pervert. I know what you're really
here for, you cheek freak.
Well, guess what? If you try and catch
these buns, you'll be catching these
hands. Now go and fetch me my towel. I
don't want him to laugh at me for having
giant booty cheeks.
Why the hell did you two tie him up like
a piñata in my living room? Are you
going to shove candy up his ass? Cut him
down and treat our guest with respect.
>> But what if he tries to [__] you?
>> Then I'll have a damn good time. Bulk,
give me your pocketk knife so I can cut
him down and take off that stupid robe.
I said we aren't doing that cult [__]
>> You're lucky we reached you in time with
some band-aids, T- Rick. Otherwise,
you'd be dead.
>> You saved me.
>> That's right. And now you have to pay us
back. Pull down your pants and bend
over.
>> Calm your tits, Sparky. T-Rex survival
is a moment of celebration for us all.
Now he can help us in our own quest.
>> Hold on. What kind of quest are we
talking about here? Because I can't be
out very late since my bedtime is 7:00.
And if one of my gay dads finds out I'm
out of the house past that, he's going
to be pissed. And my other gay dad is
going to hit me with his belt on the
ass. Oh my god. Bulk my gay
ex-boyfriend.
>> Howdy, sugar tits. I hope life has been
treating you better than I treated your
gaping [__] after I [__] it.
>> We're going to hunt down all of the
[__] that did us harm.
>> Then we'll overthrow Princess Celestia
and Spike will be the god of the new
world. Are you in or what?
>> Dude, if it helps me get payback on
Starlight Glimmer for killing my gay
boyfriend, Thorax, then I'll do
anything. I'll even suck your balls as
long as I can go home around 7. But I
can put some pillows under the blanket
so my gay dads think I'm asleep. Then I
can sneak back out.
>> Now that's what daddy likes to hear.
Welcome to the team terri. Everybody
group hug and grab and slap each other
on the ass like baseball players do
during baseball games for some reason.